<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- 1티어 -->

  <SP_ChroniclerUniform.description>A Sheepawn uniform worn by those who work alongside the Imperial Guards of the National Cemetery. They give fallen soldiers' loved ones peace of mind by chronicling the life and career of the soldier.</SP_ChroniclerUniform.description>
  <SP_ChroniclerUniform.label>Sheepawn chronicler uniform</SP_ChroniclerUniform.label>

  <SP_ChroniclerCap.description>A chronicler cap for the Sheepawn who work alongside the Imperial Guard.</SP_ChroniclerCap.description>
  <SP_ChroniclerCap.label>Sheepawn chronicler cap</SP_ChroniclerCap.label>


  <!-- 2티어 -->

  <SP_WorkClothes.description>A thin, simple dress. It's often used in the workplace where clothes get dirty easily.</SP_WorkClothes.description>
  <SP_WorkClothes.label>Sheepawn work clothes</SP_WorkClothes.label>


  <!-- 1티어 -->

  <SP_WorkHairband.description>A simple hairband that holds a Sheepawn's hair back while she works.</SP_WorkHairband.description>
  <SP_WorkHairband.label>Sheepawn work hairband</SP_WorkHairband.label>

  <SP_SummerDress.description>A light dress mainly worn in the summer. It would go well with a picnic hat, wouldn't it?</SP_SummerDress.description>
  <SP_SummerDress.label>Sheepawn summer dress</SP_SummerDress.label>

  <SP_PiknicStrawHat.description>A cute straw picnic hat with a red ribbon.</SP_PiknicStrawHat.description>
  <SP_PiknicStrawHat.label>Sheepawn straw picnic hat</SP_PiknicStrawHat.label>


  <!-- 2티어 -->

  <SP_NurseUniform.description>A white nurse's uniform. The wool is used to bandage a Bori's wounds. The white cloth can be ripped off and used as a bandage in an emergency, but it is not as effective.</SP_NurseUniform.description>
  <SP_NurseUniform.label>Sheepawn nurse uniform</SP_NurseUniform.label>

  <SP_NurseCap.description>A nursing cap with the universal symbol of a healthcare worker on it.</SP_NurseCap.description>
  <SP_NurseCap.label>Sheepawn nurse cap</SP_NurseCap.label>


  <!-- 3티어 -->

  <SP_Special.description>For your special someone.</SP_Special.description>
  <SP_Special.label>Sheepawn special services uniform</SP_Special.label>

  <SP_BellTag.description>A necklace worn around the neck of a shepherd when the Bori and Sheepawns were migrating in search of paradise.\n\nThe clear sound of the bell calms the shepherd's flock. In their society, shepherding is a highly respected profession.\n\n\n\nWhen you grow up and go out into the world, be a guide to those lost in the abyss.\nBe the shepherd leading the lost lambs to paradise.\n\nBut mother. I don't know the way to paradise\n\nParadise is both everywhere and nowhere, all at once.\nPeople who desire the same kind of paradise come together to protect each other, and that is paradise.\n\nIs paradise... family?\n\nYes. It seems you've finally found your way.</SP_BellTag.description>
  <SP_BellTag.label>Sheepawn bell</SP_BellTag.label>


</LanguageData>